[{"question": " hey, it\u0092s your thanksgiving too, y'know, instead of watching football, you could help.", "answer": " we will.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " okay, rachel, you wanna put the marshmellows in concentric circles.", "answer": " no mon, you want to put them in concentric circles. i want to do this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " y'know, for once, i am going to sit down and try to watch one of these things. .", "answer": " halftime.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " hey, who wants to ah, throw the ball around a little, maybe get a little three on three going?", "answer": " oh! that would be sooo much fun!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh, can i play too? i\u0092ve never played football, like ever.", "answer": " great, you can cover chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " no, no, no, i don\u0092t, i don\u0092t really wanna play.", "answer": " come on man! you never want to do anything since you and janice broke up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " that\u0092s not true! i wanted to wear my bathrobe and eat peanut clusters all day. i wanted to start drinking in the morning. don\u0092t say that i don\u0092t have goals!", "answer": " chandler, you have to start getting over her. all right, if you play, you get some fresh air, maybe it\u0092ll take your mind off janice, and if you don\u0092t play, everyone will be mad at you \u0091cause the teams won\u0092t be even. come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " yeah, all right, i\u0092ll play.", "answer": " yay!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " let\u0092s do it! ross?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " do you wanna play football?", "answer": " um, monica and i aren\u0092t supposed to play football.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " says who? your mom? monica and ross: yeah.", "answer": " well, every, every thanksgiving um, we used to have a touch football game called the \u0091geller bowl.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " no, no, no, you say that proudly.", "answer": " anyway, ross and i were always captains, and um, it got kind\u0092ve competitive and one year, geller bowl vi, i accidentally broke ross\u0092s nose.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " it was soo not an accident. she saw i was about to tag her, so she threw her big fat grandma arm elbow right into my face. and just keep running.", "answer": " to score the winning touchdown, by the way.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " whoa, whoa, whoa, ho, ho, ho, you did not win the game, the touchdown didn\u0092t count, because of the spectacularly illegal, oh and by the way savage nose breaking.", "answer": "  i won the game.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " oh yeah! then how come you didn\u0092t get the geller cup?", "answer": " um, there was a geller cup?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " yes, it was the trophy you got if you won the game. but our dad said, \u0091nobody won that game, \u0091 and he was sick of our fighting, so he took the trophy and....  threw it in the lake.", "answer": " and was the curse lifted?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " anyway. that\u0092s when our mom said we were not to play football ever again.", "answer": " y'know what, i think we should play a game. i mean come on, it\u0092s been twelve years.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  once!!", "answer": " all right, we\u0092re gonna play.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " okay. let\u0092s bring it in.", "answer": " wait no, honey, honey throw it to me, throw it to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  that almost hit me in the face.", "answer": " all right, we have to pick captains.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " and then tineals.", "answer": " okay, so how do we decide that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " well, why don\u0092t we just bunny up. rachel, chandler, and joey: what? monica and ross:  bunny!", "answer": " okay, looks like ross and i are captains. okay, so um, i bunnied first so that means i get to pick first. joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " monica, i\u0092m your best friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " sweetie, don\u0092t worry you\u0092ll get picked. chandler.", "answer": " ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " sweetie, now i pick you.", "answer": " you don\u0092t pick me! you\u0092re stuck with me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " okay. all right. so let\u0092s see, let\u0092s play from the trash can, to the lightpost. right. two hand touch, we\u0092ll kick off.", "answer": " all right people listen, i\u0092ve got exactly twenty-eight minutes before i have to baste again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " wow! just like in the pros.", "answer": " huddle up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  all right, huddle up, right over here.", "answer": " wait for me! wait for me! wait for me! oh cool, this is my first huddle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay, so what do you guys really think of chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " okay, phoebe you know what you\u0092re doing right?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " okay, joey\u0092s gonna catch it, and you and i are gonna block.", "answer": " what\u0092s block?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " phoebe, i thought you said you know what you\u0092re doing?", "answer": " i thought you meant in life.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oww!! son of a...!! ow! come on!", "answer": " sorry. i\u0092m sorry. y'know what, we\u0092re just gonna throw it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " score!! 7 to nothing!", "answer": "  are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " come on, let\u0092s go!", "answer": " losers walk!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " yeah, losers talk!", "answer": " no, no, no, actually losers rhyme.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  twenty-three!! seventy-four!!  you wanna go shotgun?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  i almost caught that one!", "answer": " great! now, the score is 7 to almost 7.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " okay,  this play, i want you to do a down and out to the right. okay. break!", "answer": " wait, what am i gonna do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " you, you go long.", "answer": " wait, how long?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " until we start to look very small.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " set....hike!", "answer": " one-mississippi, two-mississippi, switch! switch! switch!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " haaaaa! hey-hey, thanks for stopping our ball.", "answer": "  you are playing american football?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " yeah! wow, your like from a whole other country.", "answer": " i\u0092m dutch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " hi-hi, i\u0092m joey.", "answer": " i\u0092m margha.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry dutch, i didn\u0092t get that last little bit.", "answer": "  hey joey, do you wanna play football or you wanna..  hi, i\u0092m chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " hello, chandler.", "answer": " her name is dutch, and also marklan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " margha.", "answer": " mar-klan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " mar-gha.", "answer": " mar-haaaan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " come on guys! let\u0092s go! come on, it\u0092s second down.", "answer": " uh, hello, it\u0092s third down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " no it\u0092s not, it\u0092s second.", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " wow, what?", "answer": " it just amazes me that your still pulling stuff like this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " pulling what? it\u0092s second down.", "answer": " okay, it\u0092s second down.  take all the second downs you need.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " i heard that!", "answer": " well, i said it loud.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " well, that went well.", "answer": " i think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " y'know, i was thinking about ah, asking her for her number.", "answer": " thanks man, but i think it makes a stronger statement if i ask for it myself, y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " whoa-ho, whoa! no, i was thinking about y'know for me, as a part of that whole getting over janice thing you were talking about.", "answer": " oh, yeah, that. all right, means that much to ya, i\u0092ll let you have her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " thanks. what, let me have her?! what do mean? like if you didn\u0092t i wouldn\u0092t have a shot?", "answer": " well i don\u0092t like to say it out loud, but, yeah! don\u0092t feel bad man, we all have our strengths. you\u0092re better with numbers and stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " chandler, i want you to run a post pattern to the left, okay. and sweetie..", "answer": " yeah, i know, go long. y'know, it\u0092s like all i\u0092m doing is running back and forth from the huddle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " well ah, you wanna just stay out there?", "answer": " can i see that for second.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " what the hell\u0092s the matter with you?! this is my favourite jersey.", "answer": " well now you have two. hey, i am good at math.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " all right, that\u0092s it. y'know i was still gonna let you have her. but now, forget about it. prepare to feel very bad about yourself.", "answer": " hey! well, i\u0092ve been preparing for that my entire life! or something about you that\u0092s mean!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " oh i got it!!  oh! ew! broken boob! ow!", "answer": " pheebs, run!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " touchdown!! touchdown!!", "answer": " uh, hello, the buzzer buzzed. it doesn\u0092t count.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " after the snap!", "answer": " before the snap!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " after!!", "answer": " before!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " now, does it really matter?", "answer": " yes!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " well, okay, i made a touchdown. it was my first touchdown. so?", "answer": " oh pheebs, that\u0092s great. it doesn\u0092t count.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " does so count!", "answer": " cheater, cheater, compulsive eater.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " y'know what, that\u0092s fine, maybe you haven\u0092t grown up, but i have.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh-ho, okay.", "answer": " dead leg!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " ow! ow! okay, okay, fine, fine! all right, you wanna win by cheating, go ahead, all right. phoebe the touchdown does count, you win.", "answer": " woo-yay!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " no! listen, i\u0092m not gonna go through this with you again, okay. just once i wanna beat when you can\u0092t blame it on the broken nose, the buzzer, or the fact that you thought you were getting mono. let\u0092s just call this, tie score and it\u0092s halftime.", "answer": " okay, first of all, i don\u0092t play with cheaters, and second of all, you know i had swollen glands!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " y'know what? i\u0092ll think you\u0092ll play.", "answer": " oh really! why is that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " because the winner gets this!", "answer": " the geller cup.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " is everybody else seeing a troll doll nailed to a two by four?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " okay, where in the hell did you get that?!", "answer": " when mom and dad drove you to the hospital to get your nose fixed, i swam into the lake and fished it out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " that cup is mine!", "answer": " no it\u0092s not! you want it, you\u0092re gonna have to win it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " all right, so are we not having dinner at all?", "answer": " come on phoebe, let\u0092s go! come on, it\u0092s time to get serious, huddle up. joey, keep your head in the game.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " it\u0092s hard, y'know, his huddle is closer to dutch girl.", "answer": " all right look, if i take chandler out of the running will you be able to focus?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " what are you gonna do?", "answer": " all right, you just make sure that chandler catches the ball, i\u0092ll take care of the rest.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " break!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " whoa! whoa!! tackled by a girl! bet ya don\u0092t see that everyday, do ya?", "answer": " whoa! whoa! whoa! what\u0092s with the tackling?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " what?! i just touched him and he went over.", "answer": " okay, you wanna play rough, we can play rough.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " hey, where\u0092d you get that?", "answer": " i went really long.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " forty-two to twenty-one! like the turkey, ross is done!", "answer": " it\u0092s no surprise that your winning, \u0091cause you got to pick first, so you got the better team.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " oh, what a great argument, exhaling! all right, y'know what, i\u0092ll prove it to you, okay. i\u0092ll trade you joey for rachel, and i\u0092ll still win the game.", "answer": " what?! the guys against the girls? see, that\u0092s ridiculous monica, because i\u0092m only down by three touchdowns.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " oh, then bring it on! oh, unless of course your afraid you might lose to a bunch of girls.", "answer": " fine, fine, rachel your with monica, joey you\u0092re with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " i can not believe your trading me!!", "answer": " come on rach, come on. let\u0092s see what\u0092s it like to be on a winning team for a change.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " are you gonna let me play?", "answer": " all right then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": "  the game is over, we eat now?", "answer": " no-no-no-no, the game\u0092s not over, we\u0092re just switching teams.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " yeah, chandler finds me so intimdating that it\u0092s better if we\u0092re on the same team.", "answer": " right. okay, let\u0092s play. let\u0092s go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " no ah, hold on a second joe, where do dutch people come from?", "answer": " ah well, the ah, pennsylvania dutch, come from pennsylvania.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " and the other ah, dutch people, they come on from somewhere near the netherlands, right?", "answer": " nice try.  see the netherlands is this make believe place where peter pan and tinker bell come from.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh, my.", "answer": " enough with geography for the insane, okay? let\u0092s play some ball, guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " whoa, whoa, no, no, i-i\u0092m not playing with this guy, now.", "answer": " fine with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " okay, y'know what, let\u0092s just cut to the chase here. okay? heidi, which of my boys do you like? chandler and joey: what are you doing? what are you doing? what are you doing?", "answer": " which do i like?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " yeah, y'know for dating, general merriment, taking back to your windmill...", "answer": " well, if i had to chose right now, which by the way i find really weird, i would have to say, chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " yes!!", "answer": " wait a minute! wait a minute! she obviously didn\u0092t understand the question.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " well, you don\u0092t you have captain hook explain it to her.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, joey, that is my chose.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " i\u0092m now thinking i would like to change my answer to, no one.", "answer": " wh-what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " i now find you shallow and um, a dork. all right, bye.", "answer": " nice going. you just saved yourself a couple months of sex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " y'know what, it doesn\u0092t matter, \u0091cause she picked me. me! from now on i get the dates and you have to stay home on saturday nights watching ready, set, cook!", "answer": " save the breakthroughs for therapy, okay. the clock is ticking. we have no time, and we are losing, we are losing to girls.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " we\u0092re not gonna lose to girls.", "answer": " hey! it\u0092s 42-21!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " this sucks, i was just up by that much!", "answer": " are we playing football or what? come on you hairy-backed marries.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " we have to do this. we are playing for women everywhere. okay, just think about every lousy date that you ever had, okay, every guy who kept on the tv while you\u0092re making out...", "answer": " oh my god! you dated someone with a glass eye too?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " come on, okay, come on this is for all womankind. let\u0092s kill \u0091um!", "answer": " yeah!!! kill \u0091um!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " all right, we still have a minute and a half to go, and we\u0092re down by two points. two points....  phoebe you do a button-hook again. rachel, you go long.", "answer": " no! come on! don\u0092t make me go long. use me. they never cover me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " honey, there\u0092s a reason.", "answer": " god, i\u0092m not lame, okay. i can do something. i can throw, would you let me throw, come on this is my game too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " come on mon, let her throw the ball.", "answer": " all right rachel, you sweep behind, i\u0092ll pitch it to you, you throw it down field to phoebe. all right. break.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " thank you! break!", "answer": " thirty-two! seventy-one! hike!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " i\u0092m so sorry! are you okay?", "answer": " no! i\u0092m not okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry, they were just all coming at me, and i didn\u0092t know what to do.", "answer": "  thirty seconds left on the timer!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " okay, okay, so we get to take that stupid troll thing home!", "answer": " come on! come on! hurry! we\u0092re running out of time! huddle up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " okay. oooh! oh, this is our last huddle, yeah.", "answer": " all right, phoebe get open. rachel, go long.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": "  okay.", "answer": " break! (in slow motion, phoebe snaps the ball, rachel goes long. joey and chandler and all over phoebe, leaving rachel wide open. ross starts to rush monica, who sees phoebe is double covered, in desperation she throws to rachel. we see flying through the air, and then rachel running underneath it, then the ball, then rachel again, then the ball, then phoebe, chandler, and joey staring at it in shock. then with the grace of jerry rice", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": "  i got a touchdown! we did it!!", "answer": " hey-hey-hey rachel, funny thing. actually, the ah, end zone starts at that pole, so you\u0092re five feet short, so we win!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " let go! let go!", "answer": " let go! i\u0092m a tiny little woman!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " guys! guys! come on! it\u0092s thanksgiving, it\u0092s not important who wins or loses. the important thing is,  the dutch girl picked me! me! not you! holland loves chandler! thank you, amsterdam! good night!!", "answer": " ow!! closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " we should defiantly play football more often. maybe there\u0092s a like league we could join or something.", "answer": " isn\u0092t there a national football league.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " yes. yes, there is, they play on sundays and monday nights.", "answer": " oh shoot! i work monday nights.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " umm, this stuffing is amazing. do you think we should bring them some?", "answer": " when they\u0092re hungry enough, they\u0092ll come in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " let go!", "answer": " no! you let go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " how come it\u0092s always us left in the field holding the ball?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " gimme the this!", "answer": " let go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 313, "asentId": 314}]